Regarding the request for capturing a
thunder dragon, that's been retracted.
He said that chicken
is actually "much tastier,"
and that he'll never forget
about you until he forgets...
So that's the message from Thousand Tricks?
Will his mockery never end?!
Arnold, please calm down!
This is playing right into his hands.
Yeah.
A silly provocation.
Anything else?
Well, um...
What?
Regarding his impression of you, Arnold...
I'm so sorry! It's nothing!
What?!
Say it.
H-He said you like... big boobs...
Am I hearing this right?
Say it again.
"Arnold Hail is a level 7 big boob lover!"
What?
Did you hear that?
So he's just a perv?
Well, he looks the part.
We are now in the golden
age of big boob lovers!
Among the countless big boob lovers
in the capital of Zebrudia,
there is one big boob lover who
stands out amongst all others!
His name is the Dragon Slayer
Crashing Thunder Arnold Hail!
Everyone's talking smack
about the Falling Fog now!
Will the time when they can
restore their honor ever come?
This way, Lady Éclair.
Wow, so this is your clan house, Ark?
I suppose it's somewhat spacious.
Well, no. I don't own this place.
Episode 12
If Possible, I'd Like to Get It
"If Possible, I'd Like to Get It."
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
Thousand Tricks is impossible to read.
Once that gravity magic wore off,
we were essentially unscathed.
He continues to provoke and incite us.
And to top it off, he wants us to fight
against his clan's strongest parties?
What the hell is his objective?!
I don't know.
I've never met a hunter like that before.
I'm back.
Oh. Welcome back.
So, how'd it go?
Well...
Huh?
We don't get into meaningless fights.
What?!
Obsidian Cross
I'm guessing Krai tricked you into this?
Here.
I'll buy you a drink.
Are you kidding me, honestly?
Starlight
Why would we ever fight for the sake
of some weakling human? Honestly!
Um...
We do not serve that man.
We will not be a stepping stone.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Isn't it obvious?
Ark Brave
Are you stupid?
You shouldn't take his words at face value.
Are you dumb?
I got basically the same
answer from each of them.
What the hell is wrong with him?
He's their clan master,
and that's how they see him?
Arnold, let's take a step back for now.
What?
Seems there's a big auction
coming up soon.
We could get our hands on some new gear
and maybe even sell that thing we have,
the one they refused to appraise
back in the Land of Fog...
You mean that strange relic?
Well, maybe we can at least
get some drinking money out of it.
Thousand Tricks...
Just this once, I'll leave it be.
Just this once!
This relic... Miss, did you find it?
Yes!
Master told me there was one over
at the Alleyne Pillars Ruins.
Huh?
That's a level 1 vault, you know.
Those rarely have any relics.
Well, Tino did try her best.
Unfortunately, this is an extraneous relic.
A different type than the ones
usually found in vaults.
It's probably something from a highly
advanced magic civilization.
So, what's it do?
You fool!
If one could tell without activating it,
appraisers would be doomed!
Sorry, Miss, but I'm going
to have to keep this for now.
With the auction coming up, I'm
drowning in appraisal requests.
Thank you.
So, can I finally see 'em?
The relics that will go up for
auction are in the back, right?
You brat...
So that's why you're here.
My admission ticket.
Huh?
I don't have time for this!
Have a quick look and get outta here!
I got it.
Why don't you just chat with Tino?
Sheesh.
Miss, are the hunts going well?
Yes, they're going well.
I'm glad to hear it.
Looking at you reminds me
of my own granddaughter.
Always remember to take
good care of your health.
Yes, sir!
Steps is a big clan.
If anything goes wrong,
ask your clanmates for help.
And Krai... Well, depending on
the situation, he may be useful.
Say what you will, but he's raised
his level more than anyone
else in the last few years.
Yes!
Master is an amazing person.
He's strict, but he's amazing.
He's got a lot of debt, but he's amazing.
Compared to him, I'm really nothing at all.
Good grief...
Hey, boy!
What the hell are you teaching this girl?!
Hey. Hey!
Are you listening?!
A mask?
Could it possibly be...
A Reversible Face?
The design does look a little different,
but this has to be one.
I used to love using these.
Just put it on, and you've
got a different face!
It's creepy!
Liz broke the previous one...
But if I had this, I could freely walk
outside without bodyguards again.
I won't be bothered by Arnold.
I could go to all the
dessert shops that I want!
I want this.
I want it so much!
Hey. Hey!
You're still not done, boy?
I've got work to do.
I'd like to talk to this item's owner
and negotiate with them directly.
Will you contact them for me?
What?!
It's not appraised yet...
That's creepy.
Master, what are you going
to do about the money?
I finally found it.
I can't let that relic slip away from me.
I'm sure I can get it cheaper
than at the auction.
A relic like that could be
used for criminal purposes,
so they don't often appear in stores.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
I'm so lucky!
Sitri said that she has so many expenses
from her research these days
that she hardly has any money on hand.
Really?
Yes.
And she's given the valuable magic-recovery
potions she had mass-produced to the mages.
Urgh... honestly.
Here.
One more to reinvigorate your tired body.
They must have been the ones
she used for recharging the relics.
W-Well, I'm sure it'll be fine.
It'll work out. It's gotta work out.
Yes, yes!
If that armband we handed in to be
appraised turns out to be highly valuable,
that would solve your money problems.
Well, that's true.
But if the relic is that rare,
I'd rather keep it for myself.
On the other hand...
Cough it up!
If I ask Liz, she'll collect money by force.
It would be great to have another
option besides Sitri for a quick loan.
Huh?
An aristocrat's crest?
That's the House of the Earl
of Gladis, right?
He famously hates the hunters,
so I wonder what he's doing here at Steps?
Lady Éclair.
I apologize for being unable to
entertain you properly.
Do not worry.
I simply wished to see where
you usually spend your days.
I dislike the vulgarity of most
hunters, but you're different.
You're much more refined.
I look forward to studying
the blade with you again.
Certainly. It would be my honor.
Hmm?
The hell are you looking at?
Get lost.
Y-You think you can talk to Master like th—
Hello, Krai.
Allow me to introduce the daughter
of the Earl of Gladis, Lady Éclair.
This is our clan master, Krai Andrey.
A pleasure.
So you're Thousand Tricks?
I've heard much about you from my father.
You appear to be as exceptionally
weak as I've been told.
I find it completely unbelievable
that someone like you
could have a higher level than Ark Rodin.
The Explorers' Association
must truly have fallen.
Perhaps you bought your level with coin?
Your poor upbringing is clearly apparent, you
ill-mannered lout. Have some sense of shame!
You... Why do you remain silent,
even after I've berated you so?
Have you no pride?!
I wasn't raised well, and I am ill-mannered,
so I try to keep my mouth
shut as much as possible.
Huh?
Oh, uh... Huh... I see.
Th-That's a good way to be.
My lady, it is time to go.
O-Oh. Yes, I see.
Well then, Ark.
Let us meet again!
Indeed.
I'm sorry to have sprung that on you.
She wanted to bring me back by
carriage, and I couldn't refuse.
That doesn't matter at all.
You returned at the perfect time.
Ark... do you have any money?
Not for you.
Let me guess: you laid eyes on a new relic?
It's almost auction season, after all.
This is different, Ark!
It's a dangerous relic.
I really want it.
Nothing is different at all.
How much do you need?
Whatever you have.
Why do you need that relic? What can it do?
That, I can't tell you.
Then it's no deal.
I see.
Hey, Sven!
Could you lend me some money?
Or Marietta or Lyle?
Oh, Thalia is an alchemist, right?
Krai really is an amusing guy!
Hey, have you heard?
It seems like Thousand Tricks asked
Ark Rodin to lend him money.
Sounds like there's a relic
he can't live without.
How much could it cost?
I'd love to see it.
Thousand Tricks'...
...treasure...
...an unbelievable...
...find!
A legendary...
...all-powerful relic!
I'm really sorry, Sitri.
We just talked about how I'd
repay you the other day...
but I'm already asking for another favor.
Even to bargain with the
relic's owner for me...
Don't worry about it.
I mean, it's you and me.
My research will be delayed a bit,
but I've sold some of my surplus materials,
so I have some cash on hand.
You want to have this relic
at any cost, right?
Yeah, basically.
If it's not enough, I'll talk to
the bank about getting a loan.
You really want this relic, don't you?
Uh, well. Yes.
We can worry about me later.
I'll make do until then.
After all, it's for a relic
you desperately desire.
Well, if it comes down to it, we'll
just deal with the relic's owner directly.
I'm good at negotiations.
Y-Yeah.
It has a bit of a disturbing appearance,
so I don't think it'll fetch a high price.
I hope the relic's owner will let us have
it for 30 million and call it a day.
Welcome.
Thank you so much for agreeing to
negotiate with us today, Arnold.
I'll just say this.
That mask is a rare item we brought
all the way from the Land of Fog.
As you can imagine, it was quite difficult.
We won't sell it for cheap.
I am well aware.
But I also hear it's creepy and unsightly.
And it's not like Krai wants
to have it at any cost.
Well, it's not like we're
desperate to sell, either!
If you're trying to take advantage of us,
we're fine with putting
it up at the auction.
I don't mean to be blunt,
but the nobility won't be
interested in such an unattractive item.
I'm afraid you aren't likely to
get a good price for it.
This isn't a fair negotiation.
We don't know what that mask can do.
But you two must have some idea,
which is why you want it.
Without knowing that,
we cannot name a price.
Instead of selling it on
the cheap like a total fool,
I'd rather destroy it.
Answer me, Thousand Tricks.
What does the mask do?
That I cannot say.
But if my predictions are right,
that relic is a bit dangerous.
Even in this country, there are laws that
restrict its use. It's best to get rid of it.
Then why do you want it?
Well, that's because... well...
He is utterly unprepared
for this negotiation.
He thinks I'll just let it go now?
Did he really believe he could
convince me like that?
Wait!
Is it a trap?!
Could it be that his actual aim
is to make us keep the mask?
Let's say that mask is actually dangerous.
Knowing that,
Thousand Tricks secretly tried to
acquire it before it went up for auction.
But when he realized that we owned it,
he instantly changed his strategy.
By goading us so blatantly
to get rid of it,
he's trying to manipulate me
into holding on to it...
10 million gil.
A-Are you sure, Arnold?
Yes. According to him,
this relic is a bit dangerous.
Do you have any objections, Thousand Tricks?
Uh, no. None at all.
I have no idea how dangerous
this relic actually is,
but we can't use it either way.
Dancing to his tune and holding
on to it would be the worst move.
In which case, naming a high price that
he can't refuse is the best course of action.
You thought you fooled us,
but too bad, Thousand Tricks.
Your pathetic face says it all:
I'm the winner here!
You think it's okay for
us to get it this cheap?
Why not?
They made the offer, after all.
All right, then.
The deal is 10 million gil for the relic.
We'll pay in cash right no—
Stop right there!
Stop right there?!
I'll give you double!
Please sell it to me!
I'll give you 20.5 million!
20.8 million!
In that case, 30 million!
30.2 million here!
30.5 million!
100 million gil.
I, Éclair Gladis, will buy
this all-powerful relic.
Any complaints?
And this is why I hate the nobility.
Why?
How did this happen?
Rumors began to spread saying you asked
Ark and the others for a loan.
And that it was to purchase a
unique, all-powerful relic.
So it's going on auction after all?
That's right.
The local authorities deemed
a direct sale logistically unfeasible.
The hubbub caught the eye
of aristocrats and merchants,
so they will be in the running as well.
Apparently, it's guaranteed to
sell for over 100 million.
Right?
I knew it.
It cannot be appraised!
The risk factor of using it is S!
Tens or hundreds of millions for
this frightening mask of dubious use?!
Why did you let rumors lead you astray?
There's no relic that can
make you all-powerful!
Who even started saying this
relic was all-powerful?
The only use for it is to go to dessert
shops without anyone knowing...
So what will you do now?
What do you mean?
Okay, fine.
I can't go taking on more debt.
That's right.
At any rate, you need to hold off
on buying more relics and such.
Krai, I got the money!
Let's give them a proper fight.
I kept it a secret from my big sister,
but I've been saving up funds
for our wedding, Krai.
It's 800 million gil.
800 million?!
The money was always for Krai, anyway.
So I was thinking we could
use it a bit earlier...
Enough is enough!
Virtually all party breakups are
due to financial or romantic quarrels!
Not to mention, your enabling
him is why Krai is so undisciplined.
Undisciplined or whatever else he may be,
I'll take him in, so no need to worry.
That's not what this is about!
I'm saying, please do not allow our
clan master to go further into debt!
Even Krai has to think about his standing!
And this is why I hate
the nobility and merchants!
Your preferences aren't
what matters here!
I don't like all this strife.
It should all be love and peace.
Krai, do you want to go
scout out that rich girl?
Maybe we can win her over if we figure
out why she wants the relic herself.
Oh, sure.
Let's do that.
I'm done.
You have quite the nerve to show up
here so brazenly, Thousand Tricks!
I see that your courage
could even rival Ark's.
No, no. The only place where
I exceed Ark is in level.
There is talk of Ark and
myself being rivals,
but it's not like that at all.
We're on completely
different playing fields.
He's just a friend to me.
A friend.
What?
Don't be so humble.
Well, I guess the treasure vaults we
complete are always higher than his.
But I think Ark still wins.
Krai, whose side are you on?
I mean, I'm on your side.
I understand what you two came here to say.
You came here to mock Ark!
You scrounged together all those relics,
then used their power
to achieve your level 8!
Your strength is false—
nothing but borrowed power!
I swear, I will definitely give
that all-powerful relic to Ark!
Your days at the top are numbered!
That wouldn't help.
Huh?
Speaking as his friend,
Ark won't be happy to get such a thing.
One relic alone wont make you the best.
The strong are strong with or without relics.
And the weak are weak.
That's right.
Even without relics, Ark is strong.
And even with relics, I'm weak.
Shut up!
Shut up, shut up!
You're an idiot! A total idiot!
You think I'm going to let us lose to you?
I'm going to get that relic for sure!
We have readied 200 million.
You have 100 million...
Even the daughter of the House of Gladis
must have some limit on her spending.
It would be wise to give up.
This is our absolute limit.
If you're prepared to spend more than that,
we will admit defeat.
You are competing against Thousand Tricks.
Yet for us to back down now would be a stain
on the name of the House of Gladis.
Our ancestors would never forgive us.
Montaure, how much can we use?
We can spend 500 million
from this house's savings.
Another 500 million could be
loaned from the Welz Trading Company.
We'd incur quite a lot of interest,
but we could procure even more.
Father, please wait!
That woman has an absolute
upper limit of 200 million.
If we can put up a little more
than 200 million, I can win.
Nobody would honestly reveal
their hand to a competitor.
You're going up against
Thousand Tricks and his ilk.
It's doubtful even 1 billion
would be enough.
Make no mistake.
This is only a loan.
I will not tolerate frivolous spending.
Yes, sir.
Éclair, you had better win this.
That is an order.
The House of Gladis has no use for losers.
Bear full responsibility
for this and go win!
Yes, sir!
Man, this has gotten so weird.
An auction isn't a war.
It's a joyous festival.
Which is why, once it ends,
we need to throw a party.
On Ark's tab!
Zebrudia Auction!
The total debt is in the billions!
By: The Grieving Heroines?
We're facing the auction of chaos!
It rains, it floods.
Anyway, it's a mission!
Zebrudia Auction!
From one to the next...
They're put up for sale!
The very, very enticing...
Collection!
Next time!
On Let This Grieving Soul...
...Retire!
Now this is what I call...
Episode 13
I Want to Win the Bid No Matter What
...the Kraimax!
Ew.
"I Want to Win the Bid No Matter What"!